1. click
5. waitForElementVisible
9. delay
13. setText
17. setText
21. setText
25. selectOptionByLabel
29. setText
33. Statement - randomNum = new java.util.Random().nextInt(1000000) + 1
37. Statement - randomEmail = emailAddress - "@gmail.com" + "+" + randomNum + "@gmail.com"
41. setText
47. If user has no email address, change the "noEmail" variable to true
51. setText
55. setText
59. setText
63. setText
67. selectOptionByLabel
71. setText
77. Must select the same test object as the "Check" step below (the clinic that this user is a patient of)
83. To change the clinic, change to the appropriate test object. Don't forget to change "Scroll to Element" step's test object to the same site
87. scrollToElement
91. click
95. waitForElementVisible